<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backdoor on wroot</title>
    <link>http://wroot.org/tags/backdoor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backdoor on wroot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:13:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wroot.org/tags/backdoor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Babadook: Connection-less Powershell Persistent and Resilient “Backdoor”</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/babadook-connection-less-powershell-persistent-and-resilient-backdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 14:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/babadook-connection-less-powershell-persistent-and-resilient-backdoor/</guid>
      <description>At my previous company I used to prank the colleagues who left their stations unlocked. I call this my &amp;#8220;internal awareness program&amp;#8221;.
It was all fun and games at the beginning. I would leave post-its on their monitors with a friendly message &amp;#8220;You could&amp;#8217;ve been hacked&amp;#8221; but it wasn&amp;#8217;t giving the expected results. Some colleagues found it funny and started &amp;#8220;collecting&amp;#8221; my post-its. There was a guy in particular with 5 of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling functions without their names in PHP</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/calling-functions-without-their-names-in-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 23:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/calling-functions-without-their-names-in-php/</guid>
      <description>Strings. Ah juicy and precious strings! It is common for malware scanners and IDPS to look for suspicious strings in network traffic and files&amp;#8230; but what if there are no strings to look for? (whaaa?)
Today I was wondering about some features found in many interpreted languages of listing its internal functions in some sort of list/array. This way we can enumerate the [index] =&amp;gt; function_name relationship, replace all function_names on the code to their index and voilá!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuxnet targets SCADA systems via USB drives vectors</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/stuxnet-targets-scada-systems-via-usb-drives-vectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 16:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/stuxnet-targets-scada-systems-via-usb-drives-vectors/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft disclosed a zero-day flaw on Windows Shell on Friday and Stuxnet (W32.Stuxnet) is already exploiting it to gain access to SCADA systems through its attack vector.
Since SCADA systems are updated mainly by CDs or pen drives, the attack vector fits as a glove. The malware targets Siemens&amp;#8217; Simatic WinCC software and intends to steal information like projects schematics and upload them to an external website.
From CNet:
 Once the malware locates the data it is looking for it encodes it and attempts to upload it to a remote server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>