<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wincc on wroot</title>
    <link>http://wroot.org/tags/wincc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wincc on wroot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:43:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wroot.org/tags/wincc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of the W32.Stuxnet SCADA threat</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/anatomy-of-the-w32-stuxnet-scada-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 13:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/anatomy-of-the-w32-stuxnet-scada-threat/</guid>
      <description>Symantec released an in-depth analysis of W32.Stuxnet, reviewed through IDA-PRO. The analysis shows off the staged infection process, the unusual injection of legitimate services instead of issuing LoadLibrary calls, core encryption and exported functions.
Tofino Security (specialized on SCADA security) has released an excellent white paper on the case (requires [free] registration). If you are a Malware Researcher / Reverse Engineer or just curious, I totally recommend it.
There&amp;#8217;s code, great explanation, images, graphs and such explaining it all the process from infection, rooting and the propper malware code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuxnet targets SCADA systems via USB drives vectors</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/stuxnet-targets-scada-systems-via-usb-drives-vectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 16:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/stuxnet-targets-scada-systems-via-usb-drives-vectors/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft disclosed a zero-day flaw on Windows Shell on Friday and Stuxnet (W32.Stuxnet) is already exploiting it to gain access to SCADA systems through its attack vector.
Since SCADA systems are updated mainly by CDs or pen drives, the attack vector fits as a glove. The malware targets Siemens&amp;#8217; Simatic WinCC software and intends to steal information like projects schematics and upload them to an external website.
From CNet:
 Once the malware locates the data it is looking for it encodes it and attempts to upload it to a remote server.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>