<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robotics / Automation on wroot</title>
    <link>http://wroot.org/categories/robotics-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robotics / Automation on wroot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 20:33:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wroot.org/categories/robotics-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iran hijacked US Drone by hacking GPS</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/iran-hijacked-us-drone-by-hacking-gps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2011 20:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/iran-hijacked-us-drone-by-hacking-gps/</guid>
      <description>These past weeks I&amp;#8217;ve been following the US drone hijacking by the Iranian Revolutionary Guards.
Recently the details of the hacking were posted.
The IRG says the communication signals were jammed forcing the UAV to go into autopilot (RTL &amp;#8211; Return To Land, to be more precise). Then the GPS signals were spoofed to make the drone think that Iran Base was his Base.
US experts are still questioning these claims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endpoint DLP: Is hardware access control enough?</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/endpoint-dlp-is-hardware-access-control-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 02:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/endpoint-dlp-is-hardware-access-control-enough/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve stumbled on this article about using a custom-built hardware to bypass hardware enforcement on most DLP solutions available on market.
The solution uses an Atmel&amp;#8217;s AVR microcontroller (the same on the Arduino&amp;#8216;s I&amp;#8217;ve been playing around lately) and the V-USB library to create a virtual USB device and is crafted to announce itself as HID (Human-interface device). What common hardware fits this description: the keyboard. As you are not likely to forbid keyboard access to your users (or else they wouldn&amp;#8217;t be able to type and thus work), this will gracefully pass through many enforcements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>