<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Network Security on wroot</title>
    <link>http://wroot.org/categories/network-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Network Security on wroot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 16:40:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://wroot.org/categories/network-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m speaking at Hackers 2 Hackers Conference 9th edition – 2012 @ São Paulo, Brazil!</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/im-speaking-at-hackers-2-hackers-conference-9th-edition-2012-sao-paulo-brazil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 16:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/im-speaking-at-hackers-2-hackers-conference-9th-edition-2012-sao-paulo-brazil/</guid>
      <description>Hi folks! I&amp;#8217;m glad to inform that my paper &amp;#8220;Advanced DDoS techniques: Layer 7, load-balancing and mobile tools&amp;#8221; was accepted by the 9th Hackers 2 Hackers Conference (H2HC).
The event will take place on October 20-21 and it seems to be another success just like previous editions.
Don&amp;#8217;t forget to check the event&amp;#8217;s website for full line-up. If you can, enroll and enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WPA faces new threat ‘Hole 196’ and new key bruteforcing service</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/wpa-faces-new-threat-hole-196-and-new-key-bruteforcing-service-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2010 16:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/wpa-faces-new-threat-hole-196-and-new-key-bruteforcing-service-2/</guid>
      <description>WPA was hit hard these days by a rumor of a new threat called &amp;#8216;Hole 196&amp;#8217;.
The hole would allow GTK (Group Temporal Key) spoofing forcing users to send the rogue AP their private key information leading to a awesome no-footprinted (medium is over air!) man-in-the-middle attacks.
To understand transient keys over WPA, Md Sohail Ahmad from AirTight said:
 WPA2 uses two types of keys: 1) Pairwise Transient Key (PTK), which is unique to each client, for protecting unicast traffic; and 2) Group Temporal Key (GTK) to protect broadcast data sent to multiple clients in a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating the risk on an ARP poison attack</title>
      <link>http://wroot.org/posts/mitigating-the-risk-on-an-arp-poison-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2010 23:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wroot.org/posts/mitigating-the-risk-on-an-arp-poison-attack/</guid>
      <description>ARP poisoning is a technique quite simple to be applied and allows traffic to be sniffer over a switched network. It can be used to sniff the connection on-the-fly and capture plain-text password or hashes. ARP poison also allows combination with other attacks such as DNS spoof and packet filters in order to deploy client side exploits transparently.
This attack can only be performed from the local network because ARP packets aren&amp;#8217;t routed so you can&amp;#8217;t hop between LANs but it can be performed from any machine on the same network so it is a serious concern when dealing with unhappy employees, interns and industrial espionage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>